<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <id>http://developer.github.com/</id>
  <title>GitHub API Changes</title>
  <updated>2014-12-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/" />
  <link rel="self" href="http://developer.github.com/changes.atom" />
  <author>
    <name>technoweenie</name>
    <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-12-12:/changes/2014-12-12-replace-older-ssh-keys-created-by-your-application/</id>
    <title type="html">Replace older SSH keys created by your application</title>
    <published>2014-12-12T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-12-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>jasonrudolph</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-12-12-replace-older-ssh-keys-created-by-your-application/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Back in February, we &lt;a href="/changes/2014-02-24-finer-grained-scopes-for-ssh-keys/#keys-are-now-immutable"&gt;improved the security audit trail for SSH keys&lt;/a&gt;. Soon, organizations will be able to block access for SSH keys that were created prior to those improvements. If your application relies on &lt;a href="/guides/managing-deploy-keys/#deploy-keys"&gt;deploy keys&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="/v3/users/keys/"&gt;user keys&lt;/a&gt; for repository access, we recommend replacing any keys created before February 24, 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To ensure that your application is not affected by organizations blocking access to these keys, &lt;strong&gt;you should replace the affected keys by January 15, 2015&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="how-should-you-replace-these-keys"&gt;How should you replace these keys?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We recommend the following steps for identifying and replacing the affected keys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="identify-the-affected-keys"&gt;1. Identify the affected keys&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You only need to replace keys that your application created prior to February 24, 2014. If you don’t know when your app created a given key, you can get the creation timestamp from the API. The &lt;code&gt;created_at&lt;/code&gt; property is available for &lt;a href="/v3/repos/keys/"&gt;deploy keys&lt;/a&gt; and for &lt;a href="/v3/users/keys/#list-your-public-keys"&gt;user keys&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="inform-the-affected-users"&gt;2. Inform the affected users&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you know which keys you need to replace, we recommend that you inform the affected users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For security, GitHub automatically sends an email to a user whenever a new SSH key is added to their account. Similarly, when a new deploy key is added to a repository, GitHub sends an email to the repository’s administrators. When you replace your application’s old keys with new ones, GitHub will email the affected users. To avoid surprising those users, you should alert them that you’ll be replacing your keys. You may want to include a link to this post in your message.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="add-a-new-key"&gt;3. Add a new key&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use the API to add the new &lt;a href="/v3/repos/keys/#create"&gt;deploy key&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="/v3/users/keys/#create-a-public-key"&gt;user key&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="delete-the-old-key"&gt;4. Delete the old key&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once your application is using the new key, use the API to delete the old one. There’s an &lt;a href="/v3/repos/keys/#delete"&gt;API for deleting deploy keys&lt;/a&gt; and an &lt;a href="/v3/users/keys/#delete-a-public-key"&gt;API for deleting user keys&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="were-here-to-help"&gt;We’re here to help&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, if you have any questions or concerns, please &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Replace+SSH+keys+created+by+application"&gt;get in touch&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-12-09:/changes/2014-12-09-new-attributes-for-stars-api/</id>
    <title type="html">New Attributes for Starring API</title>
    <published>2014-12-09T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-12-09T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>arfon</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-12-09-new-attributes-for-stars-api/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;You can now see when a user starred a repository. To receive the new response format containing the &lt;code&gt;starred_at&lt;/code&gt; field, request the new media type:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;curl -H "Accept: application/vnd.github.v3.star+json" https://api.github.com/users/andrew/starred
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note the starred repository is now available in the repo field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="feedback"&gt;Feedback&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or feedback about these changes, please &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=New+Attributes+for+Starring+API"&gt;drop us a line&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-12-08:/changes/2014-12-08-removing-authorizations-token/</id>
    <title type="html">Removing token attribute from Authorizations API responses</title>
    <published>2014-12-08T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-12-08T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>ptoomey3</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-12-08-removing-authorizations-token/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Since OAuth access tokens function like passwords, they should be treated with
care. Today we are making it easier to more securely work with authorizations
via the Authorizations API. We are deprecating the use use of the &lt;code&gt;token&lt;/code&gt;
attribute in the majority of the &lt;a href="/v3/oauth_authorizations/"&gt;Authorizations API&lt;/a&gt;
responses. For the &lt;a href="/v3/oauth_authorizations/#deprecation-notice"&gt;affected APIs&lt;/a&gt;, the
&lt;code&gt;token&lt;/code&gt; attribute will soon return an empty string. To get ready for that
change, we are giving developers a chance to
&lt;a href="#preview-period"&gt;preview the updated API&lt;/a&gt; starting today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="whats-changing"&gt;What’s changing?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The current &lt;a href="/v3/oauth_authorizations/"&gt;OAuth Authorizations API&lt;/a&gt; requires GitHub to store the full value for
each OAuth token on our servers. In order to increase the security for our
users, we are changing our architecture to store the SHA-256 digest of OAuth
tokens instead. GitHub securely hashes user passwords using bcrypt and we want
to provide comparable security for OAuth tokens as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rest assured that this change is an entirely proactive measure from GitHub and is not associated with any security incident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="who-is-affected"&gt;Who is affected?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This change affects any code that relies on accessing the &lt;code&gt;token&lt;/code&gt; attribute from
&lt;a href="/v3/oauth_authorizations/#deprecation-notice"&gt;these OAuth Authorizations API responses&lt;/a&gt;.
For example, our own &lt;a href="https://mac.github.com/"&gt;GitHub for Mac&lt;/a&gt; and
&lt;a href="https://windows.github.com/"&gt;GitHub for Windows&lt;/a&gt; applications relied on reading the &lt;code&gt;token&lt;/code&gt;
from the &lt;a href="/v3/oauth_authorizations/#get-or-create-an-authorization-for-a-specific-app"&gt;Get-or-create an authorization for a specific app&lt;/a&gt; API, in order to support multiple installations of our desktop application for a single user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="what-should-you-do"&gt;What should you do?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to reduce the impact of removing the &lt;code&gt;token&lt;/code&gt; attribute, the OAuth
Authorizations API has added a new request attribute (&lt;code&gt;fingerprint&lt;/code&gt;), added
three new response attributes (&lt;code&gt;token_last_eight&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;hashed_token&lt;/code&gt;, and
&lt;code&gt;fingerprint&lt;/code&gt;), and added &lt;a href="/v3/oauth_authorizations/#get-or-create-an-authorization-for-a-specific-app-and-fingerprint"&gt;one new API&lt;/a&gt;.
While these new APIs and attributes do not replace the full functionality that
previously existed, they can be used in place of &lt;code&gt;token&lt;/code&gt; for most common use cases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;token_last_eight&lt;/code&gt; returns the last eight characters of the associated OAuth
token. As an example, &lt;code&gt;token_last_eight&lt;/code&gt; could be used to display a list of
partial token values to help a user manage their OAuth tokens.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;hashed_token&lt;/code&gt; is the base64 of the SHA-256 digest of the token.
&lt;code&gt;hashed_token&lt;/code&gt; could be used to programmatically validate that a given token
matches an authorization returned by the API.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;fingerprint&lt;/code&gt; is a new optional request parameter that allows an OAuth
application to create multiple authorizations for a single user. &lt;code&gt;fingerprint&lt;/code&gt;
should be a string that distinguishes the new authorization from others
for the same client ID and user.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;For example, to differentiate installations of a desktop application across
multiple devices you might set &lt;code&gt;fingerprint&lt;/code&gt; to
&lt;code&gt;SHA256_HEXDIGEST("GitHub for Mac - MAC_ADDRESS_OF_MACHINE")&lt;/code&gt;. Since
&lt;code&gt;fingerprint&lt;/code&gt; is not meant to be a user-facing value, you should still set
the &lt;code&gt;note&lt;/code&gt; attribute to help a user differentiate between authorizations on their
&lt;a href="https://github.com/settings/applications"&gt;OAuth applications listing on GitHub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/v3/oauth_authorizations/#get-or-create-an-authorization-for-a-specific-app-and-fingerprint"&gt;Get-or-create an authorization for a specific app and fingerprint&lt;/a&gt;
is a new API that is analagous to the
&lt;a href="/v3/oauth_authorizations/#get-or-create-an-authorization-for-a-specific-app"&gt;Get-or-create an authorization for a specific app&lt;/a&gt;
API, but adds support for the new &lt;code&gt;fingerprint&lt;/code&gt; request parameter.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id="preview-period"&gt;Preview period&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are making the new Authorizations API available today for developers to
preview. During this period, we may change aspects of these endpoints. If we do,
we will announce the changes on the developer blog, but we will not provide any
advance notice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While these new APIs are in their preview period, you’ll need to provide the
following custom media type in the Accept header:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;application/vnd.github.mirage-preview+json
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We expect the preview period to last 4-6 weeks. (Stay tuned to the developer blog for updates.) At the end of the preview period, these changes will become an official and stable part of GitHub API.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="migration-period"&gt;Migration period&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the preview period, we will announce the start of a migration period. Developers will have 8 weeks to update existing code to use the new APIs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="why-sha-256-over-bcrypt"&gt;Why SHA-256 over bcrypt?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some users may be curious why we are not using bcrypt to hash our OAuth tokens
like we do for user passwords. Bcrypt is purposefully computationally expensive
in order to mitigate brute force attacks against low entropy passwords. However,
OAuth tokens are highly random and are not susceptible to brute force attacks.
Given that OAuth token validation occurs for each request to the API we chose
SHA-256 for performance reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or feedback, please &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Removing+authorizations+token"&gt;drop us a line&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-12-08:/changes/2014-12-08-organization-permissions-api-preview/</id>
    <title type="html">Preview the upcoming organization permission changes</title>
    <published>2014-12-08T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-12-08T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>jakeboxer</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-12-08-organization-permissions-api-preview/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE (2014-12-12):&lt;/strong&gt; The &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/#list-your-organizations"&gt;List your organizations&lt;/a&gt; API is now included in this preview as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have some upcoming changes that will affect the way organization members and repositories are managed. The most important changes are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Owners team will no longer be special.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href="/v3/repos/#list-your-repositories"&gt;List your repositories&lt;/a&gt; API will include organization-owned repositories.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/#list-user-organizations"&gt;List user organizations&lt;/a&gt; API will only include public organization memberships.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/#list-your-organizations"&gt;List your organizations&lt;/a&gt; API will require &lt;code&gt;user&lt;/code&gt; scope or &lt;code&gt;read:org&lt;/code&gt; scope.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id="whats-happening-to-the-owners-team"&gt;What’s happening to the Owners team?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently, members of your Owners team are administrators of your organization. Soon, your Owners team will become a totally normal team. Adding and removing Owners team members won’t change their administrator status anymore. Instead, you’ll be able to directly grant admin permissions to your organization’s members without adding them to any special teams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We won’t delete your Owners team, but you’ll be able to delete or rename it yourself if you want. Organizations created after the change won’t have an Owners team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="what-should-you-do"&gt;What should you do?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In preparation for this change to the Owners team, we’re releasing a few new APIs. You’ll be able to use these APIs to manage organization admins without relying on the Owners team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id="adding-an-organization-admin"&gt;Adding an organization admin&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add a new organization admin, use the new &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/members/#add-or-update-organization-membership"&gt;Add or update organization membership&lt;/a&gt; endpoint, specifying a role of &lt;code&gt;"admin"&lt;/code&gt; in the request body. This replaces adding or inviting people to the Owners team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id="removing-an-organization-admin"&gt;Removing an organization admin&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To remove someone from the organization role but keep them as a member of their teams, use the new &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/members/#add-or-update-organization-membership"&gt;Add or update organization membership&lt;/a&gt; endpoint, specifying a role of &lt;code&gt;"member"&lt;/code&gt; in the request body. This replaces removing people from the Owners team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id="listing-organization-admins"&gt;Listing organization admins&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To get a list of all your organization’s admins, use the &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/members/#members-list"&gt;Organization members list&lt;/a&gt; endpoint, specifying a role of &lt;code&gt;"admin"&lt;/code&gt; in the query string. This replaces listing the members of the Owners team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id="checking-if-someone-is-an-organization-admin"&gt;Checking if someone is an organization admin&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To check if a given user is an organization admin, use the new &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/members/#get-organization-membership"&gt;Get organization membership&lt;/a&gt; endpoint. If the returned &lt;code&gt;"role"&lt;/code&gt; attribute is set to &lt;code&gt;"admin"&lt;/code&gt; and the returned &lt;code&gt;"state"&lt;/code&gt; attribute is set to &lt;code&gt;"active"&lt;/code&gt;, the user is an organization admin. This replaces checking if a user is on the Owners team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="whats-happening-to-the-list-your-repositories-api"&gt;What’s happening to the “List your repositories” API?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently, the &lt;a href="/v3/repos/#list-your-repositories"&gt;List your repositories&lt;/a&gt; API only returns repositories that are owned by users, not by organizations. If you want a list of &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt; the repositories that the authenticated user has access to, you need to use multiple API methods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soon, this API will include all repositories that the authenticated user has access to (whether they’re owned by a user or by an organization).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="what-should-you-do-1"&gt;What should you do?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many apps use the &lt;a href="/v3/repos/#list-your-repositories"&gt;List your repositories&lt;/a&gt; API in conjunction with the &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/#list-your-organizations"&gt;List your organizations&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="/v3/repos/#list-organization-repositories"&gt;List organization repositories&lt;/a&gt; APIs to build up a list of all the repositories the authenticated user has access to. If your app is doing this, you’ll be able to get rid of all the organization-related API calls and just use the &lt;a href="/v3/repos/#list-your-repositories"&gt;List your repositories&lt;/a&gt; API.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your app uses the &lt;a href="/v3/repos/#list-your-repositories"&gt;List your repositories&lt;/a&gt; API for another purpose, you’ll need to update your app to handle the new organization-owned repositories we’ll be returning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="whats-happening-to-the-list-user-organizations-api"&gt;What’s happening to the “List user organizations” API?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/#list-user-organizations"&gt;List user organizations&lt;/a&gt; API is intended provide &lt;a href="https://help.github.com/articles/publicizing-or-concealing-organization-membership"&gt;public organization memberships&lt;/a&gt; for any user. When you use this API to fetch &lt;em&gt;your own&lt;/em&gt; organizations, this API currently returns your public and private organization memberships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soon, this API will only return public organization memberships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="what-should-you-do-2"&gt;What should you do?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your app uses the &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/#list-user-organizations"&gt;List user organizations&lt;/a&gt; API to fetch all of the organization memberships (public and private) for the authenticated user, you’ll need to update your app to use the &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/#list-your-organizations"&gt;List your organizations&lt;/a&gt; API instead. The &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/#list-your-organizations"&gt;List your organizations&lt;/a&gt; API returns all organizations (public and private) that your app is authorized to access.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="whats-happening-to-the-list-your-organizations-api"&gt;What’s happening to the “List your organizations” API?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OAuth requests will soon require minimum &lt;a href="/v3/oauth/#scopes"&gt;scopes&lt;/a&gt; in order to access the &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/#list-your-organizations"&gt;List your organizations&lt;/a&gt; API.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently, the API response always includes your &lt;a href="https://help.github.com/articles/publicizing-or-concealing-organization-membership"&gt;public organization memberships&lt;/a&gt;, regardless of the OAuth scopes associated with your request. If you have &lt;code&gt;user&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;read:org&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;write:org&lt;/code&gt;, or &lt;code&gt;admin:org&lt;/code&gt; scope, the response also includes your private organization memberships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soon, this API will only return organizations that your authorization allows you to operate on in some way (e.g., you can list teams with &lt;code&gt;read:org&lt;/code&gt; scope, you can publicize your organization membership with &lt;code&gt;user&lt;/code&gt; scope, etc.). Therefore, this API will require at least &lt;code&gt;user&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;read:org&lt;/code&gt; scope. (&lt;code&gt;write:org&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;admin:org&lt;/code&gt; scope implicitly include &lt;code&gt;read:org&lt;/code&gt; scope.) OAuth requests with insufficient scope will receive a &lt;code&gt;403 Forbidden&lt;/code&gt; response.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="what-should-you-do-3"&gt;What should you do?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you &lt;a href="/v3/auth/#via-username-and-password"&gt;authenticate via username and password&lt;/a&gt;, you are not affected by this change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your app only needs to fetch the user’s public organization memberships, you should use the &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/#list-user-organizations"&gt;List user organizations&lt;/a&gt; API instead. Since that API only returns public information, it does not require any scopes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="preview-period"&gt;Preview period&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting &lt;strong&gt;today&lt;/strong&gt;, these new APIs are available for developers to preview. We expect the preview period to last for four weeks. (Stay tuned to the developer blog for updates.) At the end of the preview period, these additions will become official components of the GitHub API.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While these additions are in their preview period, you’ll need to provide the following custom media type in the &lt;code&gt;Accept&lt;/code&gt; header:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;application/vnd.github.moondragon-preview+json
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the preview period, we may change aspects of these endpoints. If we do, we will announce the changes on the developer blog, but we will not provide any advance notice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="migration-period"&gt;Migration period&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the preview period, we will announce the start of a migration period. At that time, developers should update their applications to use the new APIs for managing organization admins. During this period, you will still be able to use the Owners team to manage your organization’s admins, so that you have time to update your applications to use the new APIs without breakage. We expect the migration period to last for four weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the migration period, the Owners team will no longer be special, and you’ll no longer be able to rely on it for managing organization admins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or feedback, please &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Organization+Admin+Pre-release+Preview"&gt;get in touch with us&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-12-03:/changes/2014-12-03-preview-the-new-organization-webhooks-api/</id>
    <title type="html">Preview the New Organization Webhooks API</title>
    <published>2014-12-03T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-12-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>jdpace</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-12-03-preview-the-new-organization-webhooks-api/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today we’re very excited &lt;a href="https://github.com/blog/1933-introducing-organization-webhooks"&gt;to announce Organization Webhooks&lt;/a&gt;.
Organization Webhooks allow you to subscribe to events that happen across an
entire organization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to being able to subscribe to the existing repository oriented
events across an organization, we’re also adding some new events which are
exclusive to organization webhooks. The new &lt;a href="/v3/activity/events/types/#repositoryevent"&gt;&lt;code&gt;repository&lt;/code&gt;
event&lt;/a&gt; allows you to receive webhook payloads when a new
repository is created. By subscribing to the &lt;a href="/v3/activity/events/types/#membershipevent"&gt;&lt;code&gt;membership&lt;/code&gt;
event&lt;/a&gt;, you’ll be notified whenever a user is added or
removed from a team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re making this new API for Organization Webhooks available today &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/hooks/#preview-period"&gt;for
developers to preview&lt;/a&gt;. The preview period will allow us to &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Organization+Webhooks"&gt;get
your feedback&lt;/a&gt; before declaring the Organization Webhooks API final.
We expect the preview
period to last for roughly 30-60 days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we discover opportunities to improve the API during the preview period, we
may ship changes that break clients using the preview version of the API. We
want to iterate quickly. To do so, we will announce any changes here (on the
developer blog), but we will not provide any advance notice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of preview period, the Organization Webhooks API will become an
official component of GitHub API v3. At that point, the new Organization
Webhooks API will be stable and suitable for production use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hope you’ll take it for a spin and &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Organization+Webhooks"&gt;send us your feedback&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-11-25:/changes/2014-11-25-the-deployments-api-is-official/</id>
    <title type="html">The Deployments API is official</title>
    <published>2014-11-25T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-11-25T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>atmos</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-11-25-the-deployments-api-is-official/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We’re happy to announce that the &lt;a href="/v3/repos/deployments"&gt;Deployments API&lt;/a&gt; is officially part
of GitHub API v3. We now consider it stable for production use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to everyone who provided feedback during the preview period. We got
some great feedback, and hope this feature helps you build the tools you
need to make GitHub the best place to ship exactly the way you want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="preview-media-type-no-longer-needed"&gt;Preview media type no longer needed&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you used the Deployments API during the preview period, you needed to
provide a custom media type in the &lt;code&gt;Accept&lt;/code&gt; header:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;application/vnd.github.cannonball-preview+json
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that the preview period has ended, you no longer need to pass this custom
media type.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead, we &lt;a href="/v3/media"&gt;recommend&lt;/a&gt; that you specify &lt;code&gt;v3&lt;/code&gt; as the version in the
&lt;code&gt;Accept&lt;/code&gt; header:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;application/vnd.github.v3+json
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h3 id="feedback"&gt;Feedback&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ll never be done listening to you! As always, please don’t hesitate to
&lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Deployments+API"&gt;share your feedback&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-10-29:/changes/2014-10-24-status-api-limits/</id>
    <title type="html">Status API Limits</title>
    <published>2014-10-29T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-10-29T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>rsanheim</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-10-24-status-api-limits/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;To ensure a high level of service for all API consumers, we will soon limit the number of &lt;a href="/v3/repos/statuses/"&gt;statuses&lt;/a&gt;
to 1000 per commit SHA, repository, and context.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beginning Monday, November 3rd, we will trim existing data sets that exceed this limit, deleting the oldest 
records first.  Attempts to create statuses beyond that limit will result in a &lt;a href="https://developer.github.com/v3/#client-errors"&gt;validation error&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any feedback or questions, please don’t hesistate to &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Combined+Status+API"&gt;contact&lt;/a&gt; us.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-10-21:/changes/2014-10-21-deployment-webhook-payload-changes/</id>
    <title type="html">Deployment webhook payload changes</title>
    <published>2014-10-21T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-10-21T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>atmos</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-10-21-deployment-webhook-payload-changes/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;On November 4th, 2014, we will begin sending a new format for &lt;a href="https://developer.github.com/v3/activity/events/types/#deploymentevent"&gt;deployment&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://developer.github.com/v3/activity/events/types/#deploymentstatusevent"&gt;deployment status&lt;/a&gt; payloads for webhooks. In the meantime we’ll be running in a compatability mode that will give integrators the time needed to start taking advantage of the new format. Integrators who are working with webhooks and deployments are advised to upgrade to the new payload format to avoid service interruption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This change brings the payloads for these events more inline with the responses you’d receive from the API. Instead of having deployment and deployment status attributes as top-level keys, we will now nest them under &lt;code&gt;deployment&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;deployment_status&lt;/code&gt; keys. Since we’re still in the &lt;a href="https://developer.github.com/changes/2014-01-09-preview-the-new-deployments-api/"&gt;preview period&lt;/a&gt; for the deployments API we felt it was best to correct this inconsistency now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="deploymentevent-changes"&gt;DeploymentEvent Changes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h4 id="old-format"&gt;Old Format&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-javascript highlight"&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"id"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="mi"&gt;42&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"sha"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"deadbeef"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"ref"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"master"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"task"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"deploy"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"name"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"my-org/our-app"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"environment"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"production"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"payload"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"description"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"Deploying master"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"repository"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"sender"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="p"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h4 id="current-format---20141022"&gt;Current Format - 2014/10/22&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-javascript highlight"&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"id"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="mi"&gt;42&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"sha"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"deadbeef"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"ref"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"master"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"task"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"deploy"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"name"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"my-org/our-app"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"environment"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"production"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"payload"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"description"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"Deploying master"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"repository"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"deployment"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"url"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://api.github.com/repos/my-org/our-app/deployments/42"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"id"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="mi"&gt;42&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"sha"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"deadbeef"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"ref"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"master"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"task"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"deploy"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"environment"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"production"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"payload"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"description"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"Deploying master"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"creator"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"created_at"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"2014-09-23T16:37:49Z"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"updated_at"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"2014-09-23T16:37:49Z"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"statuses_url"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://api.github.com/repos/my-org/our-app/deployments/42/statuses"&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"sender"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="p"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h4 id="new-format---20141105"&gt;New Format - 2014/11/05&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-javascript highlight"&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"deployment"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"url"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://api.github.com/repos/my-org/our-app/deployments/42"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"id"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="mi"&gt;42&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"sha"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"deadbeef"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"ref"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"master"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"task"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"deploy"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"environment"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"production"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"payload"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"description"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"Deploying master"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"creator"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"created_at"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"2014-09-23T16:37:49Z"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"updated_at"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"2014-09-23T16:37:49Z"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"statuses_url"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://api.github.com/repos/my-org/our-app/deployments/42/statuses"&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"repository"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"sender"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="p"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h2 id="deploymentstatusevent-changes"&gt;DeploymentStatusEvent Changes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h4 id="old-format-1"&gt;Old Format&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-javascript highlight"&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"id"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="mi"&gt;2600&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"state"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"success"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"deployment"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"target_url"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://gist.github.com/deadbeef"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"description"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"Deployment was successful"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"repository"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"sender"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="p"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h4 id="current-format---20141022-1"&gt;Current Format - 2014/10/22&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-javascript highlight"&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"id"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="mi"&gt;2600&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"state"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"success"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"target_url"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://gist.github.com/deadbeef"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"description"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"Deployment was successful"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"repository"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"deployment_status"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"url"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://api.github.com/repos/my-org/our-app/deployments/42/statuses2600"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"id"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="mi"&gt;2600&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"state"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"success"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"creator"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"target_url"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://gist.github.com/deadbeef"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"description"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"Deployment was successful"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"created_at"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"2014-09-23T16:45:49Z"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"updated_at"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"2014-09-23T16:45:49Z"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"deployment_url"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://api.github.com/repos/my-org/our-app/deployments/42"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"repository_url"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://api.github.com/repos/my-org/our-app"&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"deployment"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"sender"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="p"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h4 id="new-format---20141105-1"&gt;New Format - 2014/11/05&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-javascript highlight"&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"deployment_status"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"url"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://api.github.com/repos/my-org/our-app/deployments/42/statuses2600"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"id"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="mi"&gt;2600&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"state"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"success"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"creator"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"target_url"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://gist.github.com/deadbeef"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"description"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"Deployment was successful"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"created_at"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"2014-09-23T16:45:49Z"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"updated_at"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"2014-09-23T16:45:49Z"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"deployment_url"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://api.github.com/repos/my-org/our-app/deployments/42"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"repository_url"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://api.github.com/repos/my-org/our-app"&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"deployment"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"repository"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"sender"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="p"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or feedback, please &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Deployments+API"&gt;get in touch&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-10-16:/changes/2014-10-16-removed-ssl-version-3-support-from-webhooks-and-services/</id>
    <title type="html">Removed SSLv3 support from webhooks and services</title>
    <published>2014-10-16T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-10-16T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>kdaigle</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-10-16-removed-ssl-version-3-support-from-webhooks-and-services/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This morning, we &lt;a href="https://github.com/github/github-services/pull/949"&gt;removed support&lt;/a&gt; for the &lt;code&gt;ssl_version&lt;/code&gt; webhook configuration
option and made &lt;code&gt;TLS 1.X&lt;/code&gt; the default cryptographic protocol to address the &lt;a href="https://www.openssl.org/~bodo/ssl-poodle.pdf"&gt;POODLE exploit&lt;/a&gt;.
You should no longer set or rely on the &lt;code&gt;ssl_version&lt;/code&gt; configuration option.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or feedback, please &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Removed+SSLv3+support+from+webhooks+and+services"&gt;drop us a line&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-10-06:/changes/2014-10-06-new-attributes-for-issue-events-api/</id>
    <title type="html">New Attributes for Issue Events API</title>
    <published>2014-10-06T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-10-06T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>jdpace</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-10-06-new-attributes-for-issue-events-api/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We’ve made it easier to track changes to issues. The Issue Events API now provides more context for several event types:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
&lt;code&gt;assigned&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;unassigned&lt;/code&gt; events now include an &lt;code&gt;assignee&lt;/code&gt; object so you can see just who was assigned or unassigned.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
&lt;code&gt;labeled&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;unlabeled&lt;/code&gt; events include a &lt;code&gt;label&lt;/code&gt; object.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
&lt;code&gt;milestoned&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;demilesoned&lt;/code&gt; events include a &lt;code&gt;milestone&lt;/code&gt; object.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
&lt;code&gt;renamed&lt;/code&gt; events include a &lt;code&gt;rename&lt;/code&gt; object with the title before and after the rename.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href="/v3/issues/events/"&gt;Issue Events API documentation&lt;/a&gt; for a full list of supported events. If you have
any questions or feedback, please &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=New+Attrs+for+Issue+Events+API"&gt;drop us a line&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-09-23:/changes/2014-09-23-one-more-week-before-the-add-team-member-api-breaking-change/</id>
    <title type="html">One more week before the "Add team member" API breaking change</title>
    <published>2014-09-23T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-09-23T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>jakeboxer</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-09-23-one-more-week-before-the-add-team-member-api-breaking-change/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE (2014-09-30):&lt;/strong&gt; In response to feedback from developers, we’re delaying the breaking change to the &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/teams/#add-team-member"&gt;“Add team member” API&lt;/a&gt; until Monday, &lt;strong&gt;October 6, 2014&lt;/strong&gt;. The change will go into effect for all requests on that date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting October 6, if you use &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/teams/#add-team-member"&gt;the “Add team member” API&lt;/a&gt; to add a user to a team and that user isn’t already on another team in your organization, the request will fail. To avoid this, be sure to use the &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/teams/#add-team-membership"&gt;the “Add team membership” API&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="the-organization-and-team-membership-apis-are-now-official"&gt;The Organization and Team Membership APIs are now official&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As promised in &lt;a href="/changes/2014-09-16-finalizing-the-organization-and-team-membership-apis/"&gt;our blog post earlier this month&lt;/a&gt;, the &lt;a href="/changes/2014-08-28-accepting-organization-invitations-from-the-api/"&gt;Organization Membership&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="/changes/2014-08-05-team-memberships-api/"&gt;Team Membership&lt;/a&gt; APIs are now an official part of the GitHub API! The preview media type is no longer required to access them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or feedback, please &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Organization+and+Team+Membership+APIs"&gt;get in touch with us&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-09-16:/changes/2014-09-16-finalizing-the-organization-and-team-membership-apis/</id>
    <title type="html">Finalizing the Organization and Team Membership APIs</title>
    <published>2014-09-16T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-09-16T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>jakeboxer</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-09-16-finalizing-the-organization-and-team-membership-apis/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;For the past few weeks, the new &lt;a href="/changes/2014-08-28-accepting-organization-invitations-from-the-api/"&gt;Organization Membership&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="/changes/2014-08-05-team-memberships-api/"&gt;Team Membership&lt;/a&gt; APIs have been available for early access via a preview media type.  As of today, these APIs are stable and suitable for production use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="preview-period-ends-on-september-23"&gt;Preview period ends on September 23&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On September 23, 2014, these APIs will become official parts of the GitHub API v3. At that time, the preview media type will no longer be required to access these APIs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="reminder-breaking-change-to-legacy-endpoint"&gt;Reminder: Breaking change to legacy endpoint&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/teams/#add-team-member"&gt;breaking change to the “Add team member” endpoint&lt;/a&gt; will also go into effect for all requests on &lt;strong&gt;September 23, 2014&lt;/strong&gt;. At that time, if you use the &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/teams/#add-team-member"&gt;add team member&lt;/a&gt; endpoint to add a user to a team and that user isn’t already on another team in your organization, the request will fail. To avoid this, be sure to use the &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/teams/#add-team-membership"&gt;add team membership&lt;/a&gt; endpoint.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="addition-to-the-organization-membership-api"&gt;Addition to the Organization Membership API&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to your feedback, we’ve updated the Organization Membership API to provide direct access to basic information about the organization whenever you fetch a &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/members/#list-your-organization-memberships"&gt;list of memberships&lt;/a&gt; or a &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/members/#get-your-organization-membership"&gt;single membership&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or feedback, please &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Organization+and+Team+Membership+APIs"&gt;get in touch with us&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-09-12:/changes/2014-09-12-changing-organization-feeds/</id>
    <title type="html">Changing organization feeds in the Feeds API</title>
    <published>2014-09-12T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-09-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>mastahyeti</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-09-12-changing-organization-feeds/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We have deprecated the &lt;code&gt;current_user_organization_url&lt;/code&gt; attribute and the
&lt;code&gt;current_user_organization.href&lt;/code&gt; attribute in the &lt;a href="/v3/activity/feeds/"&gt;Feeds API&lt;/a&gt;. If you make
use of these attributes, you’ll want to update your code to use the new
&lt;code&gt;current_user_organization_urls&lt;/code&gt; attribute instead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="changes-to-the-deprecated-attributes"&gt;Changes to the deprecated attributes&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Previously, the deprecated attributes returned URI template. For example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-javascript highlight"&gt;&lt;span class="s2"&gt;"current_user_organization_url"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://github.com/organizations/{org}/mastahyeti.private.atom?token=abc123"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The template included a deprecated authentication token. Our new tokens are
valid only for a concrete feed URL (not for a URI template). Because the
deprecated attributes were templates and did not specify a concrete URL, the API
could not provide a token that could be used for organization feeds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting today, the API returns empty values for the deprecated attributes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="new-attribute-for-organization-feeds"&gt;New attribute for organization feeds&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to preserve the functionality of this API, we have added a new
attribute that lists specific Atom feed urls for each of the user’s
organizations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-javascript highlight"&gt;&lt;span class="s2"&gt;"current_user_organization_urls"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://github.com/organizations/github/mastahyeti.private.atom?token=abc123"&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://github.com/organizations/requests/mastahyeti.private.atom?token=token=def456"&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="p"&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the updated &lt;a href="/v3/activity/feeds/"&gt;Feeds API documentation&lt;/a&gt; for the new fields. If you
have any questions or feedback, please &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Changing+organization+feeds+in+the+Feeds+API"&gt;get drop us a line&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-09-05:/changes/2014-09-05-removing-gravatar-id/</id>
    <title type="html">Removing Gravatar ID from user payloads</title>
    <published>2014-09-05T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-09-05T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>mastahyeti</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-09-05-removing-gravatar-id/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We have deprecated the &lt;code&gt;gravatar_id&lt;/code&gt; attribute in the &lt;a href="https://developer.github.com/v3/users/"&gt;user
representation&lt;/a&gt;. Starting September 19,
the API will always provide an empty string as the value for this attribute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users have been able to upload avatars directly to GitHub for &lt;a href="https://github.com/blog/1803-switch-your-picture-with-ease"&gt;a while
now&lt;/a&gt;. If users
haven’t uploaded an avatar, we still try to fetch one from Gravatar, but that
happens behind the scenes on GitHub’s servers. As a result, the &lt;code&gt;gravatar_id&lt;/code&gt;
attribute no longer identifies a GitHub user’s canonical avatar. Instead, API
consumers should use the &lt;code&gt;avatar_url&lt;/code&gt; to fetch a user’s avatar. The &lt;code&gt;avatar_url&lt;/code&gt;
attribute has always been present in the &lt;a href="/v3/users/"&gt;v3 user representation&lt;/a&gt;
and is the only reliable way to find a GitHub user’s avatar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or feedback, please &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Removing+Gravatar+ID"&gt;get drop us a line&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-08-28:/changes/2014-08-28-accepting-organization-invitations-from-the-api/</id>
    <title type="html">Accepting organization invitations from the API</title>
    <published>2014-08-28T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-08-28T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>jakeboxer</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-08-28-accepting-organization-invitations-from-the-api/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The upcoming &lt;a href="/changes/2014-08-05-team-memberships-api/"&gt;Team Memberships API&lt;/a&gt; gives you the power to &lt;a href="https://help.github.com/articles/adding-or-inviting-members-to-a-team-in-an-organization"&gt;invite&lt;/a&gt; new GitHub users to your organization via the API. We’re expanding the API to also allow users to view their organization membership statuses and accept any invitations they’ve received.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="the-new-organization-memberships-api"&gt;The new Organization Memberships API&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When someone &lt;a href="https://help.github.com/articles/adding-or-inviting-members-to-a-team-in-an-organization"&gt;invites&lt;/a&gt; you to an organization, your membership with that organization begins in the “pending” state. The new &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/members/#list-your-organization-memberships"&gt;list organization memberships&lt;/a&gt; endpoint allows you to find your pending memberships. You can then change them to “active” (accepting the invitation in the process) by using the &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/members/#edit-your-organization-membership"&gt;edit organization membership&lt;/a&gt; endpoint.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="new-team-membership-api-response-attribute"&gt;New Team Membership API response attribute&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Previously, responses from the &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/teams/#add-team-membership"&gt;add team membership&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/teams/#get-team-membership"&gt;get team membership&lt;/a&gt; endpoints included a “status” attribute, which could either be “active” or “pending”. We’ve renamed this attribute from “status” to “state” for better consistency with our other API calls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To give you time to update your apps, we’ll keep the legacy “status” attribute around alongside the new “state” attribute until &lt;strong&gt;September 4th, 2014&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="preview-period"&gt;Preview period&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new Organization Memberships API is available for developers to preview alongside the &lt;a href="/changes/2014-08-05-team-memberships-api/"&gt;Team Memberships API&lt;/a&gt;. During this period, we may change aspects of these endpoints. If we do, we will announce the changes on the developer blog, but we will not provide any advance notice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While these new APIs are in their preview period, you’ll need to provide the following custom media type in the &lt;code&gt;Accept&lt;/code&gt; header:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;application/vnd.github.the-wasp-preview+json
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We expect the preview period to last 30-60 days. At the end of the preview period, the Team and Organization Memberships APIs will become official components of GitHub API v3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or feedback, please &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Team+Memberships+API"&gt;get in touch with us&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-08-15:/changes/2014-08-15-deployments-api-changes/</id>
    <title type="html">New features for the Deployments API preview</title>
    <published>2014-08-15T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-08-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>atmos</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-08-15-deployments-api-changes/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We’ve added two new features to the &lt;a href="https://developer.github.com/changes/2014-01-09-preview-the-new-deployments-api/"&gt;Deployments API preview&lt;/a&gt;: the ability to query deployments and a new &lt;code&gt;task&lt;/code&gt; attribute for different types of deployment tasks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="api-changes"&gt;API changes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can now search for deployments via query parameters to the &lt;a href="https://developer.github.com/v3/repos/deployments/#list-deployments"&gt;listing endpoint&lt;/a&gt;. You can filter on &lt;code&gt;sha&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;ref&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;task&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;environment&lt;/code&gt;. This makes it easier to answer questions like “when was the last time someone deployed to staging?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre class="terminal"&gt;
$ curl -H "Authorization: token [yours]" \
       https://api.github.com/repos/octocat/my-repo/deployments?environment=staging
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h2 id="new-attribute"&gt;New attribute&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve also added a &lt;code&gt;task&lt;/code&gt; attribute to the deployment resource. The &lt;code&gt;task&lt;/code&gt; attribute allows you to specify tasks other than just pushing code. Popular deployment tools like &lt;a href="http://capistranorb.com/"&gt;capistrano&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.fabfile.org/"&gt;fabric&lt;/a&gt; support named tasks to do things like running schema migrations. We hope this attribute will give integrators the flexibility they need to provide custom functionality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or feedback, please &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Deployments+API"&gt;get in touch&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-08-05:/changes/2014-08-05-team-memberships-api/</id>
    <title type="html">We're changing the way you add new members to your organization</title>
    <published>2014-08-05T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-08-05T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>jakeboxer</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-08-05-team-memberships-api/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today, we’re announcing a change to the way organization owners add new members to their organization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Previously, if you were an organization owner, you could use the &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/teams/#add-team-member"&gt;add team member&lt;/a&gt; endpoint to add any GitHub user to any team on your organization without any sort of approval from them. Now, we’re increasing user security by sending &lt;a href="https://help.github.com/articles/adding-or-inviting-members-to-a-team-in-an-organization"&gt;invitations&lt;/a&gt; to users when they’re added to teams on organizations that they aren’t yet a part of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this change, if you use the &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/teams/#add-team-member"&gt;add team member&lt;/a&gt; endpoint to add a user to a team and that user isn’t already on another team in your organization, the request will fail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="the-new-team-memberships-api"&gt;The new Team Memberships API&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should change all your &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/teams/#add-team-member"&gt;add team member&lt;/a&gt; requests to use the new &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/teams/#add-team-membership"&gt;add team membership&lt;/a&gt; endpoint. This new endpoint works exactly the same as the old one, with one important change: if the membership being added is for a user who is unaffiliated with the team’s organization, that user will be sent an invitation via email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unlike the &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/teams/#add-team-member"&gt;add team member&lt;/a&gt; endpoint, a successful request to the &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/teams/#add-team-membership"&gt;add team membership&lt;/a&gt; endpoint does &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; guarantee that the user is now a member of the team. If you’re trying to migrate to the new endpoint and need to know when a user has been successfully added (not just invited) to a team, please check out &lt;a href="/v3/activity/events/types/#teamaddevent"&gt;TeamAddEvent&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="preview-period"&gt;Preview period&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re making the new Team Memberships API (and the breaking changes to the &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/teams/#add-team-member"&gt;add team member&lt;/a&gt; API) available today for developers to preview. During this period, we may change aspects of these endpoints. If we do, we will announce the changes on the developer blog, but we will not provide any advance notice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While these new APIs are in their preview period, you’ll need to provide the following custom media type in the &lt;code&gt;Accept&lt;/code&gt; header:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;application/vnd.github.the-wasp-preview+json
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We expect the preview period to last 30-60 days. At the end of the preview period, the Team Memberships API will become an official component of GitHub API v3, as will the &lt;a href="/v3/orgs/teams/#add-team-member"&gt;add team member&lt;/a&gt; API’s breaking changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or feedback, please &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Team+Memberships+API"&gt;get in touch with us&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-07-28:/changes/2014-07-28-assignee-and-label-actions-for-issue-events/</id>
    <title type="html">New assigned/labeled actions for issue and pull request events</title>
    <published>2014-07-28T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-07-28T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>jdpace</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-07-28-assignee-and-label-actions-for-issue-events/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;As part of the &lt;a href="https://github.com/blog/1866-the-new-github-issues"&gt;new GitHub Issues&lt;/a&gt;, we’ve added new actions to the issues and pull requests webhook events: “labeled”, “unlabeled”, “assigned”, and “unassigned”. The payload will also include the respective assignee or label for these new actions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you already have a &lt;a href="/webhooks/"&gt;webhook&lt;/a&gt; subscribed to the &lt;code&gt;issues&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;pull_request&lt;/code&gt; events, you’ll start seeing these new actions immediately. The new events can also be fetched from the &lt;a href="/v3/issues/events/"&gt;issue events API&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information, be sure to check out our documentation for the &lt;a href="/v3/activity/events/types/#issuesevent"&gt;IssuesEvent&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="/v3/activity/events/types/#pullrequestevent"&gt;PullRequestEvent&lt;/a&gt;. If you have any questions or feedback, please &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=New+Assigned+and+Labeled+Actions+for+Issues+and+Pull+Request+Events"&gt;drop us a line&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-07-09:/changes/2014-07-09-status-contexts-are-official/</id>
    <title type="html">The Combined Status API is official</title>
    <published>2014-07-09T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-07-09T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>bhuga</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-07-09-status-contexts-are-official/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We’re happy to announce that the &lt;a href="/v3/repos/statuses/#get-the-combined-status-for-a-specific-ref"&gt;Combined Status API&lt;/a&gt; is officially part
of the GitHub API v3. We now consider it stable for production use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to everyone who provided feedback during the comment period. We got
some great feedback, and hope this feature helps you build the tools you
need to make GitHub the best place to ship exactly the way you want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="preview-media-type-no-longer-needed"&gt;Preview media type no longer needed&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you used the Combined Status API during the preview period, you needed to
provide a custom media type in the &lt;code&gt;Accept&lt;/code&gt; header:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;application/vnd.github.she-hulk-preview+json
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that the preview period has ended, you no longer need to pass this custom
media type.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead, we &lt;a href="/v3/media"&gt;recommend&lt;/a&gt; that you specify &lt;code&gt;v3&lt;/code&gt; as the version in the
&lt;code&gt;Accept&lt;/code&gt; header:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;application/vnd.github.v3+json
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h3 id="feedback"&gt;Feedback&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ll never be done listening to you! As always, please don’t hesitate to
&lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Combined+Status+API"&gt;share your feedback&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-07-07:/changes/2014-07-07-example-webhook-payloads/</id>
    <title type="html">New example webhook payloads</title>
    <published>2014-07-07T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-07-07T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>kdaigle</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-07-07-example-webhook-payloads/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today, we’ve added example &lt;a href="https://github.com/blog/1778-webhooks-level-up"&gt;webhook&lt;/a&gt; payloads to the &lt;a href="/v3/activity/events/types/"&gt;event types&lt;/a&gt; page.
Alongside existing descriptions for each event, we now include an &lt;a href="/v3/activity/events/types/#issuesevent"&gt;example payload&lt;/a&gt;
so that you can quickly see the data provided by the event. You can learn more about how webhooks
work with our &lt;a href="/webhooks/"&gt;Webhooks Guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or feedback, please &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Example+webhook+payloads"&gt;get in touch&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-06-23:/changes/2014-06-23-the-github-enterprise-api-documentation-has-a-new-home/</id>
    <title type="html">The GitHub Enterprise API documentation has a new home!</title>
    <published>2014-06-23T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-06-23T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>gjtorikian</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-06-23-the-github-enterprise-api-documentation-has-a-new-home/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://enterprise.github.com"&gt;GitHub Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; offers the same set of APIs as GitHub.com, as well as its own set of Enterprise-specific functionality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The GitHub Enterprise API has been documented on &lt;a href="https://enterprise.github.com/help"&gt;the Enterprise Help site&lt;/a&gt; for some time. We’ve now &lt;a href="https://developer.github.com/v3/enterprise/"&gt;moved the resources to this site&lt;/a&gt; to be hosted alongside the rest of the GitHub API documentation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is there an API workflow you’re particularly interested in? &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Suggestion+for+an+Enterprise+Guide"&gt;Let us know&lt;/a&gt; and we’ll do our best to &lt;a href="https://developer.github.com/guides/"&gt;write a guide&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-06-19:/changes/2014-06-19-combined-status-api-pagination/</id>
    <title type="html">Pagination in the Combined Status API</title>
    <published>2014-06-19T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-06-19T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>bhuga</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-06-19-combined-status-api-pagination/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We’re getting close to bringing the &lt;a href="/v3/repos/statuses/#get-the-combined-status-for-a-specific-ref"&gt;Combined Status API&lt;/a&gt; out of preview
mode, and have just a couple of small changes to make before it’s :sparkles:.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, we’re now &lt;a href="/v3/#pagination"&gt;paginating&lt;/a&gt; combined status API calls. The combined status
&lt;code&gt;state&lt;/code&gt; field will always take all statuses into account, but we’ll now only
return 100 embedded statuses at a time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, we’re adding a &lt;code&gt;total_count&lt;/code&gt; field, mirroring the Search API. This
count represents the number of contexts submitted for the given commit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, we’re interested in &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Combined+Status+API"&gt;hearing your feedback&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-06-11:/changes/2014-06-11-improved-ci-support-for-deployments-api/</id>
    <title type="html">Improved CI support for the Deployments API</title>
    <published>2014-06-11T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-06-11T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>atmos</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-06-11-improved-ci-support-for-deployments-api/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today we’re making a few minor changes to the &lt;a href="https://developer.github.com/changes/2014-01-09-preview-the-new-deployments-api/"&gt;Deployments API preview&lt;/a&gt;. With the introduction of &lt;a href="https://developer.github.com/changes/2014-03-27-combined-status-api/"&gt;combined statuses&lt;/a&gt; in a &lt;a href="https://developer.github.com/changes/2014-04-10-deployment-api-preview-extension/"&gt;recent update&lt;/a&gt;, we noticed a few inconsistencies with the API that we’d like to remedy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re introducing a new parameter called &lt;code&gt;required_contexts&lt;/code&gt;. This parameter accepts an array of named &lt;a href="https://developer.github.com/v3/repos/statuses/"&gt;commit status&lt;/a&gt; contexts that are ensured to be in a “success” state before the deployment is created. This allows you to verify that more than one system verified your code before you deploy it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve removed support for the &lt;code&gt;force&lt;/code&gt; parameter. The force parameter existed to bypass both the auto-merge and commit status checks. The same behavior can now be accomplished by setting &lt;code&gt;auto_merge&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;required_contexts&lt;/code&gt; appropriately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re also setting a context for all &lt;a href="https://developer.github.com/v3/repos/statuses/"&gt;commit statuses&lt;/a&gt;. If a commit status is created without a context, we’ll now set it to the string “default”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or concerns, &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Deployments+API"&gt;drop us a line&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-06-09:/changes/2014-06-09-new-attributes-for-pull-request-review-comment-events/</id>
    <title type="html">New attributes for PullRequestReviewComment events</title>
    <published>2014-06-09T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-06-09T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>jdpace</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-06-09-new-attributes-for-pull-request-review-comment-events/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We’ve enhanced the &lt;a href="https://developer.github.com/v3/activity/events/types/#pullrequestreviewcommentevent"&gt;PullRequestReviewComment events payloads&lt;/a&gt; to include &lt;code&gt;action&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;pull_request&lt;/code&gt; attributes. With the addition of the &lt;code&gt;pull_request&lt;/code&gt; attribute, you now have immediate access to detailed information about the pull request without needing an additional API request.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or feedback, please &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=PullRequestReviewComment+Event+Payloads"&gt;get in touch&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-05-19:/changes/2014-05-19-deployments-api-updates/</id>
    <title type="html">New attributes for the Deployments API</title>
    <published>2014-05-19T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-05-19T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>atmos</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-05-19-deployments-api-updates/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We’re continuing to iterate on the &lt;a href="https://developer.github.com/changes/2014-01-09-preview-the-new-deployments-api/"&gt;Deployments API preview&lt;/a&gt;, and we’re starting to see it satisfy more and more use cases. Today we’re introducing new attributes for Deployments and Deployment Statuses as well as a few payload changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is a breaking change for Deployment Status payloads&lt;/strong&gt;. If you’re trying out this new API during its preview period, you’ll need to update your code to continue working with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="api-changes"&gt;API Changes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Deployments we’re introducing the concept of an &lt;code&gt;environment&lt;/code&gt;. An environment is basically a unique identifier for a deployment target. Lots of people tend toward the concept of environments for staging, QA, user acceptance testing, etc. We hope this enhancement will enable more use cases for our users that deploy to multiple environments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deployments are also persisting the requested deployment &lt;code&gt;ref&lt;/code&gt;. Previously we resolved a ref to the current SHA for that ref. Now we’ll be keeping the ref around for historical purposes. This is especially helpful if you’re deploying branches to verify them before you merge them into your default branch (e.g., “master”).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="json-payload-changes"&gt;JSON Payload Changes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re also adding a few attributes to the outbound Deployment payloads. We’re now including the &lt;code&gt;ref&lt;/code&gt; attribute so you know the branch or tag name that resolved to a specific SHA. The &lt;code&gt;environment&lt;/code&gt; is also present.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="webhook-changes"&gt;Webhook Changes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Deployment Status payloads now embed the associated Deployment object. With this enhancement, Deployment Status events received via webhooks will have enough information to notify other systems, without having to call back to the GitHub API for the &lt;code&gt;environment&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;ref&lt;/code&gt;, or payload that was deployed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="example-deployment-json"&gt;Example Deployment JSON&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-javascript highlight"&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"url"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://api.github.com/repos/my-org/my-repo/deployments/392"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"id"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="mi"&gt;392&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"sha"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"837db83be4137ca555d9a5598d0a1ea2987ecfee"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"ref"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"master"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"environment"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"staging"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"payload"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"fe"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"fe1"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"fe2"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"fe3"&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="p"&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"description"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"ship it!"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"creator"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"login"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"my-org"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"id"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="mi"&gt;521&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"avatar_url"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://avatars.githubusercontent.com/u/2988?"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"type"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"User"&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"created_at"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"2014-05-09T19:56:47Z"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"updated_at"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"2014-05-09T19:56:47Z"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"statuses_url"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://api.github.com/repos/my-org/my-repo/deployments/392/statuses"&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="p"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h3 id="example-deployment-status-json"&gt;Example Deployment Status JSON&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-javascript highlight"&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"url"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://api.github.com/repos/my-org/my-repo/deployments/396/statuses/1"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"id"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="mi"&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"state"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"success"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"deployment"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"url"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://api.github.com/repos/my-org/my-repo/deployments/396"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"id"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="mi"&gt;392&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"sha"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"837db83be4137ca555d9a5598d0a1ea2987ecfee"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"ref"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"master"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"payload"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"fe"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"fe1"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"fe2"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"fe3"&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class="p"&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"environment"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"production"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"description"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"Deploying to production"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"creator"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="p"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"login"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"alysson-goldner"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"id"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="mi"&gt;540&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"type"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"User"&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"created_at"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"2014-05-09T19:59:36Z"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"updated_at"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"2014-05-09T19:59:36Z"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"statuses_url"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://api.github.com/repos/my-org/my-repo/deployments/396/statuses"&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="p"&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"description"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"Deployment succeeded"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"target_url"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://deploy.myorg.com/apps/my-repo/logs/420"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"created_at"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"2014-05-09T19:59:39Z"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"updated_at"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"2014-05-09T19:59:39Z"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"deployment_url"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="s2"&gt;"https://api.github.com/repos/my-org/my-repo/deployments/396"&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="p"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or feedback, please &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Deployments+API"&gt;get in touch&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-05-09:/changes/2014-05-09-improved-pagination-for-the-repository-commits-api/</id>
    <title type="html">Improved pagination for the Repository Commits API</title>
    <published>2014-05-09T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-05-09T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>izuzak</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-05-09-improved-pagination-for-the-repository-commits-api/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="/v3/repos/commits/"&gt;Repository Commits API&lt;/a&gt; now supports an additional approach for paginating &lt;a href="/v3/repos/commits/#list-commits-on-a-repository"&gt;commit lists&lt;/a&gt;. As of today, this endpoint supports the “standard” &lt;a href="/v3/#pagination"&gt;&lt;code&gt;page&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;per_page&lt;/code&gt; parameters&lt;/a&gt; for controlling pagination. This API now uses these parameters by default when constructing &lt;a href="/v3/#pagination"&gt;page links&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="improved-results-and-increased-consistency"&gt;Improved results and increased consistency&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This new approach improves the reliability of this endpoint, which on rare occasions skipped some commits during pagination. This enhancement also increases the overall consistency of the API, as all endpoints now paginate resource lists the same way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="old-parameters-still-supported"&gt;Old parameters still supported&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The old way of paginating, using &lt;code&gt;top&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;last_sha&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;per_page&lt;/code&gt; parameters, is still supported in API v3, but it will be removed in the &lt;a href="https://developer.github.com/v3/versions/#v3-deprecations"&gt;next major version of the API&lt;/a&gt;. API clients that are manually constructing URLs for pages should be modified to use the new parameters. Even better, API clients shouldn’t construct URLs for pages manually, but should use &lt;a href="/guides/traversing-with-pagination/"&gt;page links provided by the &lt;code&gt;Link&lt;/code&gt; header&lt;/a&gt; in API responses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since both the new and the old pagination parameters are still supported in API v3, API clients shouldn’t notice any changes today. Still, if you notice any problems with this endpoint, please &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=API:+Commits+pagination+improvements"&gt;let us know&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-05-06:/changes/2014-05-06-gist-api-now-truncating-large-files/</id>
    <title type="html">Changes to Gist API response for large files</title>
    <published>2014-05-06T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-05-06T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>leongersing</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-05-06-gist-api-now-truncating-large-files/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In order to provide a faster, more robust API for Gist, we are making two changes to better handle large files in &lt;a href="/v3/gists/#detailed-gist-representation"&gt;Gist API responses&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="truncating-file-contents-larger-than-one-megabyte"&gt;Truncating file contents larger than one megabyte&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="/v3/gists/#detailed-gist-representation"&gt;Gist API response&lt;/a&gt; includes data for every file in the Gist. That works well for Gists with reasonably-sized files. When a Gist contains large files, however, it can lead to timeouts when preparing or sending the API response.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To eliminate those timeouts, the API now limits the amount of content returned for each file. If a file is larger than one megabyte in size, the API response will include the first megabyte of content for that file. (Few Gists have files this large. As a result, most API clients won’t notice any impact from this change.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="new-truncated-attribute"&gt;New “truncated” attribute&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The JSON snippet below illustrates the attributes provided for each file in the Gist API response. In it, you’ll notice a new &lt;code&gt;truncated&lt;/code&gt; attribute included as part of the file metadata. This Boolean attribute indicates whether the &lt;code&gt;content&lt;/code&gt; value is truncated for this request.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;{
  files: {
    "my_large_file.md": {
      "size": 2097152,
      "content": "Large content. Truncated at end of first megabyte. [...]",
      "truncated": true,
      "raw_url": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/[...]/my_large_file.md",
      "type": "text/plain",
      "language": "Markdown"
    }
  }
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h3 id="getting-the-full-content-for-truncated-files"&gt;Getting the full content for truncated files&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We recognize that sometimes you’ll still want the full content for a file, even if it’s too large to get returned in the standard Gist API response. For files under 10 megabytes, simply make a request to the URL specified in the &lt;code&gt;raw_url&lt;/code&gt; attribute, and you’ll receive the complete content for that file. For larger files, you’ll need to clone the gist locally via the &lt;code&gt;git_pull_url&lt;/code&gt; to access the full file contents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions, don’t hesitate to &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Gist+API+now+truncates+large+files"&gt;get in touch&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-04-25:/changes/2014-04-25-user-content-security/</id>
    <title type="html">New user content domains</title>
    <published>2014-04-25T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-04-25T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>azizshamim</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-04-25-user-content-security/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;h2 id="securing-your-content"&gt;Securing your content&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://bounty.github.com"&gt;GitHub Bug Bounty program&lt;/a&gt; recently identified a few cross-domain vulnerabilities related to user-generated content, and we’ve shipped improvements today to address those issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to better isolate your content from potentially malicious content uploaded by other users (e.g., content that might contain Cross-Site Scripting or other embedded attacks), we now serve user-generated content from subdomains of &lt;strong&gt;githubusercontent.com&lt;/strong&gt;. This content is no longer served from subdomains of &lt;strong&gt;github.com&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="whats-affected"&gt;What’s affected?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This change affects the following subdomains:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;raw.github.com&lt;/strong&gt; : Serves raw file content from your repository.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;embed.github.com&lt;/strong&gt; : Allows users to embed rich GitHub content on other sites.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;render.github.com&lt;/strong&gt; : Displays rich content on GitHub.com.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;f.cloud.github.com&lt;/strong&gt; : Hosts all those amazing gifs you use in Pull Requests and Issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Content formerly served by these subdomains is now served from subdomains of &lt;strong&gt;githubusercontent.com&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="older-links"&gt;Older links&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have old links to this content, don’t worry: as of today, we’re forcing the old domains to redirect to the new domains. Your existing links should continue to work automatically in your browser. If you’re using a URL from Gist or GitHub to directly access user-generated content via &lt;code&gt;curl&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;wget&lt;/code&gt;, or a library (like &lt;a href="https://github.com/jnunemaker/httparty"&gt;HTTParty&lt;/a&gt;), be sure to configure that tool to follow the redirect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="your-proxies-or-filters"&gt;Your proxies or filters&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some security systems (web proxies, for example) may not recognize the &lt;strong&gt;githubusercontent.com&lt;/strong&gt; domain. In those cases, you may need update your proxies and security software accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, if you have any questions, please &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Changes+to+user+content+domains"&gt;get in touch&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Happy and safe GitHubbing!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-04-22:/changes/2014-04-22-deprecating-beta-media-type/</id>
    <title type="html">Deprecating the beta media type</title>
    <published>2014-04-22T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-04-22T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>jasonrudolph</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-04-22-deprecating-beta-media-type/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Now that the GitHub API is &lt;a href="/changes/2014-01-07-upcoming-change-to-default-media-type/"&gt;serving the v3 media type by default&lt;/a&gt;, we are deprecating the legacy &lt;a href="/v3/versions/#beta"&gt;beta media type&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will eventually remove support for the beta media type, but we have no official retirement date to annouce at the moment. When the time comes, rest assured that we’ll announce the retirement with plenty of notice. In the meantime, existing API clients that rely on the beta media type should start making plans to migrate to v3. The beta media type differs from v3 in &lt;a href="/v3/versions/#differences-from-beta-version"&gt;just a few places&lt;/a&gt;. In most cases, migrating an application from the beta media type to the v3 media type is smooth and painless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, if you have any questions, please &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=API:+Deprecating+the+beta+media+type"&gt;get in touch&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:developer.github.com,2014-04-10:/changes/2014-04-10-deployment-api-preview-extension/</id>
    <title type="html">Extending the preview period for the Deployments API</title>
    <published>2014-04-10T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-04-10T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <author>
      <name>atmos</name>
      <uri>https://github.com/technoweenie</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://developer.github.com/changes/2014-04-10-deployment-api-preview-extension/" />
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The preview period for the new &lt;a href="/changes/2014-01-09-preview-the-new-deployments-api/"&gt;Deployments API&lt;/a&gt; continues to yield valuable feedback from developers. In early March, we used that feedback to &lt;a href="/changes/2014-03-03-deployments-api-updates/"&gt;improve the payload format&lt;/a&gt; that integrations can use to customize deployments. A few weeks later, we began integrating with the new &lt;a href="/changes/2014-03-27-combined-status-api/"&gt;Combined Status API&lt;/a&gt; to help ensure that only verified code gets deployed, even if you have multiple systems verifying different aspects of your software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To give developers time to explore these recent refinements to the Deployments API, we’re extending the preview period for a little while longer. As always, if you have any questions or feedback, please &lt;a href="https://github.com/contact?form%5Bsubject%5D=Deployments+API"&gt;get in touch&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
